Paris
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Paris
2.1.1.1.19
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1230
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - Redfern Star, circa 1910; 1; 12000; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - American shoe store, circa 1910; 2; 12001; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - A la Maison Doree, circa 1910; 3; 12002; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Au Bon Marche department store, circa 1910; 4; 12008; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Café L’Enfer, circa 1910; 5; 12010; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - The Moulin Rouge, circa 1910; 6; 12013; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Flores in pare[?] Moulan[?], circa 1910; 7; 12014; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Gardens of the Tuileries, circa 1910; 8; 12016; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Jardin des Tuileries, circa 1910; 9; 12238; 993; 4x5 (Box 1230)
  - Garden of the Luxembourg, circa 1910; 10; 12017; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Place de la Bastille and the Colonne de Juillet, circa 1910; 11; 12028; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Place de la Bastille and Colonne de Juillet, circa 1910; 12; 12029; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Residence on the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 13; 12031; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Residence, circa 1910; 14; 12032; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Baron Rothschild’s residence, circa 1910; 15; 12033; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Victor Hugo’s house, number six Place de Vosges, circa 1910; 16; 12034; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - American church, circa 1910; 17; 12035; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Hotel de Louvre, circa 1910; 18; 12036; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Business office, American Embassy, circa 1910; 19; 12037; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Gare du Nord, circa 1910; 20; 12038; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Gare du Quai-d’Orsay (Orleans Railway), circa 1910; 21; 12039; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Le Matin, taken from the corner, circa 1910; 22; 12040; 361; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Le Matin, from boulevard, circa 1910; 23; 12041; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Sign boards, circa 1910; 24; 12042; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Grand Palais where the “salon” is held, circa 1910; 25; 12043; 403; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - The opera house, circa 1910; 26; 12044; 360; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - American Express office (Place de l’Opéra), circa 1910; 27; 12045; 365; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Winter Garden, Grand Hotel, general view, circa 1910; 28; 12046; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Winter Garden, Grand Hotel, side view, circa 1910; 29; 12047; 379; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Rooftops from the Grand Hotel, circa 1910; 30; 12048; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Musée de Cluny, circa 1910; 31; 12049; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Entrance to the Musée de Cluny, circa 1910; 32; 12050; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Garden of the Musée de Cluny, circa 1910; 33; 12051; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - A corner of the garden of the Musée de Cluny, circa 1910; 34; 12052; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - French Zouaves in the garden of Musée de Cluny, circa 1910; 35; 12053; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Notre Dame Cathedral, front view, circa 1910; 36; 12054; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Notre Dame Cathedral, taken from the Petit Pont, circa 1910; 37; 12055; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Notre Dame Cathedral, full side view, circa 1910; 38; 12056; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Notre Dame Cathedral from across the river, side view, circa 1910; 39; 418; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Notre Dame Cathedral, from the rear, circa 1910; 40; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - The Seine looking toward Notre Dame Cathedral, circa 1910; 41; 12241; 4x5 (Box 1230)
  - The Trocadéro, front view showing fountains, circa 1910; 42; 12059; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Trocadéro, side view, circa 1910; 43; 417; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Below the terrace of the Trocadéro at the “cascade”, circa 1910; 44; 12247; 4x5 (Box 1230)
  - The Institut de France, circa 1910; 45; 12061; 451; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - The remains of the Bastille, circa 1910; 46; 12062; 356; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - Frank R. Roberson at the Hôtel des Invalides, Musée de l’Armée, circa 1910; 47; 12063; 453; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  - La Madeleine church, circa 1910; 48; 12064; 355; 5x7 (Box 1230)
  Box 1231
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - Steps leading to Montmartre, circa 1910; 1; 12065; 396; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Steps leading up to Montmartre, circa 1910; 2; 12066; 391; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Looking toward Montmartre, circa 1910; 3; 12067; 385; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Showing type of architecture in Montmartre, circa 1910; 4; 12068; 392; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Montmartre district, circa 1910; 5; 12250; 1020; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Looking toward the Basilique du Sacré Coeur from l’Arc de Triomphe, circa 1910; 6; 12069; 409; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Basilique du Sacré Coeur, looking up street toward church, circa 1910; 7; 12070; 381; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Basilique du Sacré Coeur, taken from below, circa 1910; 8; 12071; 378; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Horse chestnut tree in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 9; 12073; 394; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Bois de Boulogne showing road and equestrian path, circa 1910; 10; 12074; 390; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Sunday afternoon in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 11; 12075; 406; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - People in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 12; 12076; 405; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - People in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 13; 12077; 404; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Café and people, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 14; 12078; 386; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Restaurant through the trees, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 15; 12079; 395; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Pavilion Royal, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 16; 12080; 387; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Café in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 17; 12081; 435; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Park scene in Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 18; 12082; 414; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Grotto in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 19; 12083; 459; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Winding path, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 20; 12084; 383; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - By the lake, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 21; 12085; 384; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Avenue in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 22; 12086; 475; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Automobile in Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 23; 12171; 994; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Sunday afternoon in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 24; 12172; 995; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Coming from the races, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 25; 12173; 996; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Carriages in Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 26; 12174; 1001; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Bois de Boulogne on Sunday, circa 1910; 27; 12175; 1005; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Avenue in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 28; 12177; 1036; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Horse chestnut tree in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 29; 12178; 1039; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Avenue in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 30; 12179; 1043; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Automobile in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 31; 12180; 1022; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Sprinkling in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 32; 12181; 1021; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Sprinkler and automobiles in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 33; 12182; 1023; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Automobile watering cart, circa 1910; 34; 12183; 1017; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Playground, avenue in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 35; 12184; 1032; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Woman cab driver in the Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 36; 12185; 1014; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Grotto, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 37; 12186; 997; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Grotto and waterfall, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 38; 12187; 1004; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Waterfall, Bois de Boulogne, circa 1910; 39; 12188; 1006; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - River Seine, south of Paris, circa 1910; 40; 12087; 478; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Residence in a small town outside of Paris, circa 1910; 41; 12088; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Tree avenue outside Paris, circa 1910; 42; 12089; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Little village street outside Paris, circa 1910; 43; 12090; 496; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - House with vines on front, circa 1910; 44; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Small village outside Paris, circa 1910; 45; 12189; 1086; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Village street near Paris, circa 1910; 46; 12190; 1046; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Formal tree trimming, country scene, circa 1910; 47; 1084; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Horse chestnut tree roadway outside Paris, circa 1910; 48; 12195; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - French peasant woman, circa 1910; 49; 12198; 1085; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Women washing along the Seine, circa 1910; 50; 12201; 1098; 4x5 (Box 1231)
  - Pavilion Bleu Restaurant, Saint Cloud, circa 1910; 51; 12091; 506; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Château of Saint Germain, circa 1910; 52; 12092; 470; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  - Porcelain manufactory, main building, Sèvres, circa 1910; 53; 12093; 469; 5x7 (Box 1231)
  Box 1232
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - Street in Barbizon, circa 1910; 1; 12094; 426; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - House in Barbizon, circa 1910; 2; 12095; 423; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Street showing high walls of gardens, Barbizon, circa 1910; 3; 12096; 494; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Village street, Barbizon, circa 1910; 4; 12224; 1076; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Hotel opposite the Château de Fontainebleau, circa 1910; 5; 12097; 427; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Château de Fontainebleau, Cour des Adieux, circa 1910; 6; 12098; 437; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Château de Fontainebleau, Cour des Adieux, near view, circa 1910; 7; 12099; 438; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Forêt de Fontainebleau, Roches[?] de Franchard, circa 1910; 8; 12100; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Frank R. Roberson sitting at the cross in the Forêt de Fontainebleau, circa 1910; 9; 12101; 428; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Automobile at crossway, Frank R. Roberson in back seat, Fontainebleau, circa 1910; 10; 12102; 425; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Automobile at a crossways in the Fontainebleau Forest, circa 1910; 11; 12103; 424; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Avenue in the Fontainebleau Forest, circa 1910; 12; 12104; 422; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Avenue of beech trees, Forêt de Fontainebleau, circa 1910; 13; 12105; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Odd trees, Forêt de Fontainebleau, circa 1910; 14; 431; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Road to Versailles, circa 1910; 15; 12112; 479; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Hôtel de Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 16; 12113; 458; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Front of the Grand Trianon, Frank R. Roberson at right, Versailles, circa 1910; 17; 12114; 461; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Hamlet at the Petit Trianon, the dairy, Versailles, circa 1910; 18; 12115; 463; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Hamlet at the Petit Trianon, houses of Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette, Versailles, circa 1910; 19; 12116; 523; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Hamlet at the Petit Trianon, the “house” of Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette, Versailles, circa 1910; 20; 12117; 465; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Hamlet at the Petit Trianon, the mill (near view), Versailles, circa 1910; 21; 12118; 467; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Hamlet of Petit Trianon, the mill, Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson near building, Versailles, circa 1910; 22; 12119; 503; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Hamlet in the Petit Trianon, the mill (front view), Versailles, circa 1910; 23; 12120; 480; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Garden of Petit Trianon, Temple of Love, Versailles, circa 1910; 24; 12121; 504; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Temple of Love, garden of the Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 25; 12122; 472; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Formal garden in rear of Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 26; 12123; 464; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Formal garden in the rear of the Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 27; 12124; 466; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Garden at Petit Trianon, wisteria and azalea bushes, Versailles, circa 1910; 28; 12125; 524; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Wisteria in garden at Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 29; 12126; 473; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson and azalea bushes, garden of Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 30; 12128; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Gardens of the Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 31; 12129; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Rock cut walks in the gardens at Versailles, circa 1910; 32; 12130; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Gardens at Versailles, circa 1910; 33; 12131; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Part of garden at Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 34; 12132; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Walk in the gardens of the Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 35; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Frank R. Roberson at part of Palace of Versailles, circa 1910; 36; 12210; 1119; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Four French children representing two families, Versailles, circa 1910; 37; 12212; 1103; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Front of the Petit Trianon, Versailles, circa 1910; 38; 12213; 1118; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson at the Petit Trianon, camera at right, Versailles, circa 1910; 39; 12214; 1112; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Formal tree trimming, Versailles, circa 1910; 40; 12215; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Gardens, Versailles, circa 1910; 41; 474; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Entrance arch to Château de Chantilly, circa 1910; 42; 12136; 483; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Château de Chantilly, circa 1910; 43; 12137; 491; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Château de Chantilly, rear view showing gardens, circa 1910; 44; 12138; 512; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - The Gallery of Paintings, Château de Chantilly, copy, 1910 July; 45; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - The dining room, Château de Chantilly, copy, 1910 July; 46; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - The War Room, Château de Chantilly, copy, 1910 July; 47; 4x5 (Box 1232)
  - Wide tree avenue, Chantilly, circa 1910; 48; 12139; 495; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Frank R. Roberson driving automobile on road near Chantilly, circa 1910; 49; 12140; 488; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Tree avenue in the Forêt de Chantilly, circa 1910; 50; 12141; 493; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  - Near Compiègne, showing entrance to farm enclosure, circa 1910; 51; 12142; 519; 5x7 (Box 1232)
  Box 1233
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - French farm enclosure from a distance, near Compiègne, circa 1910; 1; 12143; 520; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Near Compiègne, showing extent of French farm enclosure, circa 1910; 2; 521; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - French farm enclosure near Compiègne, circa 1910; 3; 501; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Interior of French farm enclosure near Compiègne, circa 1910; 4; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Small town on way to Compiègne, circa 1910; 5; 487; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - A little village near Compiègne, circa 1910; 6; 12148; 486; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Part of old walls surrounding the town, Compiègne, circa 1910; 7; 12149; 511; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Street corner in Compiègne, circa 1910; 8; 12150; 492; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Quaint bit of old architecture, Compiègne, circa 1910; 9; 12151; 517; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Cats in front of little shop, Compiègne, circa 1910; 10; 12152; 514; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Old furniture shop, Compiègne, circa 1910; 11; 12153; 515; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Interior of bake shop, Compiègne, circa 1910; 12; 12154; 516; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Street in small village near Compiègne, circa 1910; 13; 12227; 1095; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Home near Compiègne, circa 1910; 14; 0016; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Château de Compiègne, side view toward gardens, circa 1910; 15; 12155; 513; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Château de Compiègne, front view, circa 1910; 16; 12156; 510; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Entrance to gardens, Compiègne, circa 1910; 17; 12157; 508; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Chamber of Louis XVI, Château de Compiègne, copy, 1910 July; 18; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Salle des Fêtes, Château de Compiègne, copy, 1910 July; 19; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Bedroom of Marie Antoinette, Château de Compiègne, copy, 1910 July; 20; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Bedroom of Napoleon III, Château de Compiègne, copy, 1910 July; 21; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Roadway between Compiègne and Pierrefonds, circa 1910; 22; 12158; 509; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Castle of Pierrefonds above the village, circa 1910; 23; 12163; 485; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Castle of Pierrefonds, looking through a narrow street, circa 1910; 24; 12164; 484; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Peasant homes, Pierrefonds, circa 1910; 25; 12165; 522; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Castle of Pierrefonds, side view looking up street, circa 1910; 26; 490; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Castle of Pierrefonds, general view, circa 1910; 27; 489; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Corner of castle at Pierrefonds, circa 1910; 28; 499; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Street and house with dog, Pierrefonds, circa 1910; 29; 502; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Old cathedral dating from 12th century, Senlis, circa 1910; 30; 12169; 497; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Front view of cathedral, Senlis, circa 1910; 31; 498; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Ruins of old royal palace and Gallo-Roman walls, Senlis, circa 1910; 32; 525; 5x7 (Box 1233)
  - Coming from the Longchamps races, circa 1910; 33; 12170; 1003; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - House with wisteria vines, circa 1910; 34; 12191; 1071; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Quaint house with wisteria, outside Paris, circa 1910; 35; 1101; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Railroad crossing ten minutes before train time, circa 1910; 36; 12193; 1096; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - French men on the way to enlist in the army, circa 1910; 37; 12199; 1072; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - French boys on the way to join the army, circa 1910; 38; 12200; 1081; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Church in Écouen, circa 1910; 39; 12202; 1105; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Quaint corner in Écouen, circa 1910; 40; 12203; 1100; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Dog and cat cemetery, circa 1910; 41; 12204; 1089; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Entrance to dog cemetery, circa 1910; 42; 12205; 1093; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Monument in dog cemetery, circa 1910; 43; 12206; 1092; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Gate of dog and cat cemetery, circa 1910; 44; 12207; 1091; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Frank R. Roberson on walk in dog cemetery, circa 1910; 45; 12208; 1090; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Dog cemetery, the living and the dead, circa 1910; 46; 12209; 1088; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - French gendarin [?] near Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 47; 12216; 1069; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - The Seine, near Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 48; 12217; 1068; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Tree avenue near Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 49; 12219; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Statue of Rouget de Lisle, author of the “Marseillaise”, Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 50; 12220; 1058; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Along the Seine, near Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 51; 12221; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - House in Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 52; 12222; 1067; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Free School for Boys, Choisy-le-Roi, circa 1910; 53; 12223; 1132; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Pansy bed, Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 54; 12228; 1050; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  - Picturesque corner, Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 55; 12229; 1083; 4x5 (Box 1233)
  Box 1234
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - Suspension bridge in Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 1; 12230; 1060; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 2; 12231; 1061; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Suspension bridge and observatory, Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 3; 12232; 1063; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Frank R. Roberson in corner of Buttes-Chaumont, circa 1910; 4; 12233; 1074; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French bonne in Parc Monceau, circa 1910; 5; 12234; 1034; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Le Penseur statue by Rodin in front of the Panthéon, circa 1910; 6; 12235; 1073; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Entrance to Père Lachaise Cemetery, circa 1910; 7; 12236; 1059; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - L’Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel, circa 1910; 8; 12237; 1052; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Place de la Concorde, Strossburg monument [?], circa 1910; 9; 12239; 992; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Looking sideways at l’Arc de Triomphe, circa 1910; 10; 12240; 1077; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Champs-Élysées, looking toward l’Arc de Triomphe, circa 1910; 11; 12241; 1029; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - People along the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 12; 12242; 1027; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Pont de la Concorde and the Chambre des Députés, circa 1910; 13; 12243; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Champs-Élysées from the Place de la Concorde, circa 1910; 14; 12244; 1008; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Rue Royale, circa 1910; 15; 12245; 1024; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Boulevards, circa 1910; 16; 12246; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Poorer section of the city, circa 1910; 17; 12249; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Duval Restaurant, circa 1910; 18; 12251; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Custom house gate at city limits, circa 1910; 19; 12252; 1113; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Entrance to the Metropolitan, the Parisian subway, circa 1910; 20; 12253; 1040; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Cabaret des Quat’z’Arts, circa 1910; 21; 12254; 1044; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Corner of Cooks Tourist Agency, circa 1910; 22; 12255; 1048; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French bonnes on the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 23; 12261; 1045; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French bonne on the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 24; 12262; 1028; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French nurse on the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 25; 12263; 998; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French nurse on the Champs-Élysées, circa 1910; 26; 12264; 1010; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Wagons with azaleas, coming to market, circa 1910; 27; 12266; 1107; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Azaleas coming to flower market, circa 1910; 28; 1108; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French cavalry, circa 1910; 29; 12268; 1000; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Lady cab driver, circa 1910; 30; 12269; 1018; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French boy, circa 1910; 31; 12270; 1020; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Newspaper kiosk with advertisements, circa 1910; 32; 12272; 1035; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Newspaper kiosk, circa 1910; 33; 12273; 1019; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - “Public Comfort”, circa 1910; 34; 12274; 1038; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, ice and cocoa cart, circa 1910; 35; 12275; 1042; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, advertising a cabaret, circa 1910; 36; 12276; 1016; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, priest and lame children, circa 1910; 37; 12278; 1109; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Catholic school of girls, circa 1910; 38; 12279; 1041; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Shop where funeral wreaths are sold, circa 1910; 39; 12280; 1033; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French funeral (poorer class), circa 1910; 40; 1049; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - French funeral, circa 1910; 41; 12282; 1011; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Steam train near l’Arc de Triomphe, circa 1910; 42; 12284; 1030; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Horse bus, circa 1910; 43; 12285; 1013; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Crowded horse bus, circa 1910; 44; 1002; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Motor bus, circa 1910; 45; 12286; 1015; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Book stalls along the River Seine, circa 1910; 46; 12288; 1051; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Traffic on the boulevards, circa 1910; 47; 12289; 1053; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Outdoor cafés, circa 1910; 48; 12290; 1117; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Open air cafés, circa 1910; 49; 12291; 1116; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, outdoor cafés, circa 1910; 50; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, outdoor cafés, circa 1910; 51; 1115; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Street life, girl in restaurant doorway, circa 1910; 52; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - People in carriages, circa 1910; 53; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Refreshment wagon at a railway station, circa 1910; 54; 1111; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Railroad station, circa 1910; 55; 1075; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Tourist sightseeing automobile in front of American Express, circa 1910; 56; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Veteran of Napoleonic Wars at Napoleon’s tomb, circa 1910; 57; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Lower part of the Eiffel Tower from the Trocadéro, circa 1910; 58; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Half of the Eiffel Tower from the doorway of the Trocadéro, circa 1910; 59; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Three quarters extent of the Eiffel Tower from the doorway of the Trocadéro, circa 1910; 60; 1057; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Man using saw, circa 1910; 61; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - Goats, circa 1910; 62; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - The Sorbonne, copy, 1910 July; 63; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - The Mona Lisa, Louvre, copy, 1910 July; 64; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  - The Coronation of the Virgin by Fra Angelico, copy, 1910 July; 65; 4x5 (Box 1234)
  Box 1235
- Paris, 2.1.1.1.19
  - Whales on beach near Penzauce [?], before 1916; 1; CCC; 4x5 (Box 1235)
  - Marie Antoinette going to execution, copy, before 1916; 2; 4x5 (Box 1235)
  - Marie Antoinette in the death cart, copy, before 1916; 3; 4x5 (Box 1235)
  - Marie Antoinette, copy, before 1916; 4; 4x5 (Box 1235)
  - Napoleon I, copy, before 1913; 5; 26X; 4x5 (Box 1235)